https://www.powr-flite.com/privacy-and-security/

Menu
DisinfectScrubbersCylindrical Brush ScrubbersBattery Powered Auto ScrubbersTraction Drive Auto ScrubbersAccessoriesSqueegeesBrushesPadsPad DriversBurnishersBurnishing PadsCorded BurnishersPropane BurnishersExtractorsAll Portable Carpet ExtractorsBlack Max Carpet ExtractorCarpet Extractors with HeatersSelf-Contained Carpet ExtractorsCarpet SpottersCarpet Extractor AccessoriesCarpet Extractor WandsCarpet Extractor Detail ToolsCarpet Extractor Hose CuffsWant Spray Tip ReplacementsCarpet Extractor HosesChemicalsVacuumsUpright VacuumsBackpack VacuumsCordless Backpack VacuumsWide Area VacuumsHEPA Vacuums and BagsBaglessWet Dry VacuumsSweepersToolkitsBagsDryersFloor MachinesPadsBrushesChemicalsPad DriversCarpet BonnetsSanding Pad DriverConcrete ToolsRestorationPartsVacuumsExtractorsFloor ScrubbersBurnishersJanitorialMopsCut End MopsDust MopsFinishing Wet MopHealth Care GradeLooped EndMicrofiberMop Handles/FramesSynthetic Loop EndChemicalsCartsBucketsSafety SignManualsResourcesAsk Powr-FliteGear GuideTech Support
Account
Home
Privacy and Security
Privacy and Security
Privacy Policy
Last Updated on 4-2-2019
Powr-Flite  (“Powr-Flite” “us,” or “we”) collects your personal information for a variety of reasons.  This Privacy Policy applies to personal information we collect from you in the course of our business, including information which is collected through our website, www.Powr-Flite.com, (the “Site”).You should read this Policy before using this Site or otherwise providing us with personal information.  If you choose to use the Site, you are telling us you have read and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to our actions that are consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Scope of this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies to our collection and use of the Personal Information we obtain from you, either as a result of your visit to the Site, or because you have otherwise provided us with the information.  A fuller description of this Privacy Policy’s scope, and a fuller definition of “Personal Information,” can be found below.
Information Collection
We collect Personal Information about you.  This Personal Information may include:
information about you that you provide us, for example, by registering to use the site or ordering products on the Site;
information that you otherwise provide us; and
Information we collect by automated means.
Please see below for further information about what we collect.
Information Use
We may use and transfer this Personal Information for our business purposes, including customer service and marketing to you, share this information with third parties for certain purposes, use this information to communicate with you, and use this information to comply with our legal obligations.  You have the right to review personal data collected.For more information, please review our detailed policy as further described below.
Data Security
We are concerned with the security of your Personal Information and take care in implementing appropriate physical, technical and administrative safeguards.  Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet, nor any data we collect or store, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us.  Further information on our security procedures and your responsibility for security can be found below.
Data Access, Integrity & Choice
You have choices about whether we use your Personal Information to communicate with you and, if we do communicate with you, what form that communication takes.  We will use your Personal Information as described in the “Information Use” section of this Privacy Policy.  If you wish to review the your personal data that we possess, want to request changes to your personal data, or if you want us to erase or stop using your Personal Information to communicate with you, you can write us and tell us that you no longer consent to such use (you opt-out).  Please do so by contacting us at the address below.If you opt-out, we will continue to retain and use your personal information for limited purposes.  See below for a fuller explanation.For more information regarding your options with respect to access, integrity and choice, please see below.
Effective Date and Updates
We may revise this Privacy Policy at any time.  The “Last Updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy reflects the date of the most recent revisions.  You are responsible for regularly reviewing the Privacy Policy.  The most current version of the Privacy Policy can be reviewed by clicking on the “Privacy Policy” link located at the bottom of each of our pages associated with the Site.
Contact Information
If you have questions, concerns or requests regarding Powr-Flite’s Privacy Policy, or Powr-Flite’s collection or use of your Personal Information, please contact us:3101 Wichita Ct.Fort Worth, TX 76140800-880-2913 info@powr-flite.com
Scope of this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies to our collection and use of Personal Information:
we collect or use from your visit to the Site (for example, when you register to use the site, or when we automatically collect information); and
that you provide to us by other means (for example, as part of an email you send us).
When we use the term “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we mean information that identifies, or can be used by us or on our behalf to identify, an individual.  This can be, for example, a name, street address, e-mail address, or telephone number(s).  Personal Information does not include encoded information, anonymized information, or information that is publicly available and not combined with non-public Personal Information.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We collect Personal Information from you in certain areas of the Site, as well as through your other interactions with us.  The following is a description of what Personal Information we may collect: Personal Information You Voluntarily Provide.  If you voluntarily provide us with Personal Information, for example your name, email address, phone or mobile number, or payment information (such as a credit card), we collect this Personal Information.  You may voluntarily provide this information to us in a variety of ways, including by filling out a registration form on the Site, providing us with Personal Information in order to initiate or complete a transaction, providing online feedback to us, or by contacting us (by email or otherwise) with questions about the Site or our products and services.
Personal Information We May Automatically Collect.  We use cookies and other technologies to collect information about you when you visit the Site or otherwise communicate with us.  For example, we may automatically collect information such as:
Your browser type and operating system.
Navigation and click-stream data.
Search terms you use.
Web pages you view on our Site.
Links you click.
Your IP address.
Sites you visited before coming to our Site.
Metadata from your communications with us.
IP Addresses.  An IP address is a number assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet.  As part of the protocol of the Internet, web servers can identify your computer by its IP address.  In addition, web servers may be able to identify the type of browser and/or type of computer you are using.  We collect IP addresses and related information for the purposes of system administration, to assess the traffic to the Site, and to maintain and improve the Site.  For security purposes, we may link account information you enter when you purchase products on the Site to the originating IP address, but we do not otherwise link IP addresses to your personally identifiable information.  We can and will use IP addresses and other information we possess to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use, to protect our service, the Site, customers or others, or to comply with applicable laws. Cookies.  Cookies are small bits of information that some websites (including the Site) transfer to an individual's hard drive.  We use cookies to improve users’ experience on our Site, for example to personalize features of the Site and for you, and to analyze the traffic, such as total visitors and pages viewed on the Site, and make improvements based on the data we collect.  We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies.  The use of cookies has become a standard in the industry.  Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies.  You can usually set your browser to refuse cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent.  If you refuse cookies, you may not be able to use some of the functionality of the Site.   We use cookies to personalize content and ads, provide social media recommendations and analyze website traffic. We also share information about how you use our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information you have provided to them or that they’ve collected from your use of their services. Review our full cookie policy here. Web Beacons. Web beacons are small bits of code that communicate with third parties and are embedded in web pages, our ads or in emails. We may use web beacons to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited a web page, to understand usage patterns or other third party functionality. We also may include web beacons in e-mails to learn if messages have been opened, acted on, or forwarded. You can disable the ability of Web beacons to store cookie information by declining cookies. Do Not Track.  As technologies to address Do Not Track signals are still evolving, we do not currently deploy any technology to respond to Do Not Track signals. Other Technologies.   Examples of other technologies we may use to provide better service to you include:
Web Session Variables.  Information that is passed from one web URL to another as you browse.
Browser plug-ins/add-ons.  Additional web components that may need to be installed to enable certain web features on our Site. You have the option not to install these components.
As technologies continue to evolve, we may likewise adapt our methods of collection and processing.  To the extent we understand such new technologies to materially alter our collection or use methods as described in this Policy, we will amend this Policy.The Site may contain links to websites operated by third parties.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information collected from you through such links or that you may provide on the websites you reach by those links.  We are not responsible for any actions, practices or policies of other parties. Please be advised that if you disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive information through public forums or message boards provided by Powr-Flite this information may be collected and used by others.  We do not monitor these public spaces and take no responsibility for the content, security or confidentiality of any information posted.
USE AND TRANSFER OF INFORMATION
Our use of your Personal Information for business purposes.  We may use your Personal Information for our business purposes.  Such business purposes could include, for example, using the information to provide services to you or complete a transaction with you.  We may also use this information for various other business purposes, for example:
Analyze and improve the performance of the Site.
Analyze our business, products and services.
Perform customer service.
Communicate with you regarding your account.
Communicate with you regarding products or services provided to you by us, our affiliates, or our external business partners.
Market our products and services to you.
Contact you on behalf of our affiliates or external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you.
Ask you about your experience with or opinions about our company, the Site, or our products and services.
Protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions.
Determine the effectiveness of our advertising.
Enforce our Terms and Conditions and otherwise manage our business.
Such other purposes as we disclose to you, and to which you consent, at the time we collect Personal Information from you.
Such other purposes as we disclose to you, and to which you consent, prior to our processing your Personal Information in a manner inconsistent with the terms of this Policy.
We may also provide your Personal Information to third parties who are service providers to us, for example third parties who provide computer-related, credit card processing, mapping, or debt collection services.   These third parties will only use your Personal Information as directed by us for our business purposes.Powr-Flite may also work with third parties (we call these third parties “external business partners”) to provide you with certain third party-offered products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.  We may provide your Personal Information to such third parties for their internal use, external use and analysis regarding, and communication to you about, the such products or services.  We may also share your information if we merge with, or if we or any of our assets are sold to, another company.  We may also share anonymized data derived from your Personal Information with persons performing studies in areas relevant to our business.  When we do so, we take reasonable steps to anonymize your Personal Information such that it can no longer be used to identify you. Our use of your Personal Information for legal purposes.  Sometimes a law, court order or other judicial or administrative process requires us to provide information to a government authority or party to a private lawsuit.  We will provide the information that we in good faith believe is required to comply with the law, order, or other process.  We may also disclose certain information if:
we are required to bring, or defend against, litigation or any regulatory proceeding between, or relating to, you and us,
we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may have breached our Site Terms of Use or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other Site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities, or
we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
Information Transfer.  Your Personal Information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in a country other than the one in which it was provided.  When we do so, we transfer the information in compliance with applicable data protection laws.We take steps to protect Personal Information no matter what country it is stored in or transferred to. We have procedures and controls as appropriate to help ensure this.
DATA SECURITY
We take appropriate steps that we believe are reasonable to protect the security of your Personal Information on our system, both internally and from outsiders, and to ensure the integrity of the data we collect.  We use a combination of technological, physical and policy methods to protect this data such as, for example, requiring a password to access our network and employing firewall security.  You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information.  Please be aware that we will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail.  We do not provide your password to third parties.
ACCESS, INTEGRITY & CHOICE
Access & Integrity.  If you believe that the Personal Information you voluntarily provided us is, or has become, inaccurate, incomplete or untimely, contact us and provide additional or corrected information.
Choice.  When you use the Site, or otherwise provide Personal Information to us, you consent to our using that information as described in this Privacy Policy.  If you do not want us to use or continue using your Personal Information to communicate with you, you may request that we not do so (opt-out) by following the procedures described below.
Opting-Out at Signup:  When you provide first provide us with personal information, you will be given a choice as to whether to receive promotional information from us.
Opting-Out after Signup.
If you wish to discontinue any further promotional communications from us, please send your opt-out request to our Privacy Manager at the contact information above.  Place the word “UNSUBSCRIBE” in your request to us.We also give you additional choices about how we communicate with you.
Digital / Electronic Communications.
You can also stop receiving promotional email messages from us by following the instructions provided in any such message you receive.
Continued Use of Your Personal Information Despite Opt-Out.  Because it is essential that we have and use personal information about you in order to provide you with products and services you order from us, we will continue to use personal information to facilitate a transaction that you initiate.  In addition, even if you opt-out, we will retain your personal information for our internal use, such as internal business analytics and legal compliance.  We will also retain your personal information in order to contact you for non-promotional purposes regarding your use of our service.
Sign up for news and offers
Newsletter
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
